(Flying fish)
How is it?
Hey, come out
See, very nice
I train it
How cute
Mouth keep open and close
I want to keep one too
But carp is very expensive
No such thing
one of this worth about 100000Yen
So expensive
Cool !
Why don't you keep
one too
But you have to have
a big pool at home
Sorry, my mistake
Have a big pool to
keep carp is...
What, Suneo looks down upon
you again?
Ok, we'll keep some fish
to practice
Never mind, we don't even
have fish tank
It's ok even if we don't
have anything
I've got this quartic
convenient pocket
Then you can help to get
the fish for me
Don't worry
We'll show Suneo
So reliable
Doraemon is always the best
Give me a break
Anyway, let's go fishing
Ok, let's go
Nobita, have you been
fishing before?
No
Did you hook the bite on ?
No bite
How about fish hook ?
No either
Wow
This shouldn't be a
problem then
Dorn, don't run away
stop
Broken again
Goldfish is not fun.
Let's find something else
It's better the rare ones
But those are expensive
No, it's for free
Free?
Impossible
Stop talking, just follow me
Ok, here we are, there're so
many fish
How do we catch them?
No problem! I have this
What is that ?
Don't ask. Here take some
Hold it tight now
Find the right place
Sprinkle them into the ocean
See, it's coming
The fish is flying over here
No problem!
After it eats the bite
It can swim freely in the air
Cool ! Let me try again
No,no Don't feed them too much
We can't keep them all
Never mind
Don't be so stingy
Come here little fish
How cute, how cute
Little fish are so cute
Tickles, tickles
Doraemon, help
No problem, Nobita
Fish will come to the person
feeding them
So, you're so cute
Then, follow me home
Everyone is coming with me
Honey, what would you like for
dinner tonight
How about fish ?
Fish...
Did you keep fish ?
I thought you don't have a pool
Otherwise, you can come see for
yourself
Let's all come then
It must be made out of rope
Nobita, if you lie to us
I'll won't forgive you
ls this real
Must be fake
What?
Fish flying in the air
How about it? Close to people
right?
Fish?
Fish ?
Making a circle
Fish...
Ok, thank you for doing this
How did you do this?
I asked Doraemon
To let fish live in the air
Nobita, can't tell the secret
Doraemon, I'm sorry
I forgot
Take the fish for a walk first
Come everyone
Cool, wait
I want to take a walk too
Hei...
Can't stop on the sidewalk
Cool, when did Nobita do all
training ?
I would like to keep one too
Shark, help
No problem
Look, it's very nice
It listens to me too
It hurts
Mom
I envy Nobita
Better than my carp
I'm SO angry
I knew it
He fed this to the fish
Ok...
It hurts, hurts
I got the feedings
Dorn, I'll teach him a lesson
Yes, Uncle Sailor just come
back from overseas
Good
Hello, uncle
I have a favor to ask
Want me to sprinkle this?
Try to keep it at
center of ocean
I can't hardly wait. Wonder what
fish will come
Uncle gave you this?
Wonder what is inside?
Mom, look
This is the rare flying
fish in the world
If we can keep this fish
in our house
We'll be so proud
Come out now, fish
What is this? What a
terrible fish?
That is a deep sea fish
Help, mom
It shouldn't be like this
Mom, mom
What did this happen to me?
(One inch Master)
Give me one ice cream please
Thank you for coming
Nobita
You've got something
good with you
Can I take a look
No, I want to share
with Doraemon
Hey, I didn't say
I want to eat
But...
Then let me look
I will give it back to you
But...
I said
I will give it back to you
Color and shape are both great
It's really a good thing
Yes
If the taste is good too,
then it's perfect
Delicious, taste so good
It's wonderful to have delicious
ice cream
Ok, as I promised,
I give this back to you
Why ? Don't want it ?
In that case, I'll take it
Bye now
What, snatched
Hey, I paid for it
Half of it is mine
Get my half back to me
No, it's so terrible
No...
Give my half back to me
There's no any other way
One inch Master
Let Nobita wear this
Then what?
Do you want to try ?
It'll become like this
After he shrinks,
then beat him up
It hurts, I understand now
let me change back
Take off the hat,
you'll change back
Ok, I'm going to do my best
Go for it
Dorn, Jian
I'll teach him a lesson today
R's '(Vim
Shizuka
Who?
Who is it? How disgusting
Shizuka, heysu
It's not comfortable
sitting up here
Shizuka, wait. Shizuka
I hate this
Don't
Wait Shizuka
Can't take it off
What?
Help, Doraemon Help
Need to change a pair
of glasses
Escape to this, they can't
chase me here
Help
Doraemon
I just change my glasses
Doraemon, Doraemon
Doraemon, help me
Nobita
Shizuka
You've got something
good with you
Let me borrow it
Just fora while
Don't give it to him
Nobita
Shizuka, that's trap
Jian tricked me last time
How dare you Nobita
Want to be strangled to death
“hurts
Nobita
Terrible
Caught you
Now how should I cook you ?
Jian
Be aware, Nobita
Stop, it hurts
So hurt
Ah, Nobita ?
HEY
Ah?
It hurts
Get into my back
Stop, stop it. It tickles
Stop
Nobita, I won't forgive you
It hurts. Stop Nobita.
It hurts
Tickles. Stop
Nobita
I'm so afraid of tickles
Stop. Stop it
Stop it
I can't breath now
Give me back my ice cream
Nobita, who are you talking
I know.
I'll give it back to you
Stop
Doraemon,
look I've got it back
Really
Then go eat it hurry
If we cut it in half,
there's not much left
Got it
Then, we can eat a lot
SO happy
Delicious
(Moving everywhere)
Coming, ok
Heysu, heysu
So many people are moving today
Yes
We moved too
To the side of the movie theater
Then we can snick in
from back door
We lived next to
Bolling Ally once
Before that we lived next
to fishing pool
You move a lot
Why?
It's our habit
Just move around as pleased
I've never moved
Me either
Mom, why don't we move
sometimes
Can change some feelings
What're you talking about?
Do your home walk
If you're too slow, you'll
miss the desert
Were you scolded for
something meaningless
Did you hear it
But don't you think so
People need to change
New house, new room
and new neighbors
Don't you think it's great
I guess so
Me too
Nobita, you're still pacing?
Ok, ok
I agree with Nobita
I want to move too
ls that real?
Let's try
Moving tool
It went to search for
the location
Nobita, look
You can see the scenery
from up here
Now, it's flying on top of
the school
Where do you want to move to?
Next to the theater
To the field next to theater
Field?
Set the mini house on the field
Mini house has one
blink equipment
Push the button then
we can move
Ok, finished
It can't be
Our house is next to
the theater
Are you satisfied now
Wonder if we can get in free
Let me check
Anyway, no way
It's going to be a parking
place here
What are you talking about?
I'm asking you not to build
house here
No, we live here
No good.
Hurry to move back
You old lady is so unreasonable
It's going to be a parking
place here
You are the one unreasonable
We live here
Then you better go
outside and see
Ok, go outside then
See, this is the field next to
theater
Where is theater
Where is this
Where are we? Where is this ?
Excuse me, I'm sorry
Weird
That solve one thing
Wonder if there's any other good
place
How about on top of the department
store?
Unique, seems so interesting
See, let's try
HEY
Let's go to the toy shop
Why are those people peeking us ?
Oh, no
They got into our yard
Weird, no one is home
It's not good now
It's very difficult to move
the house
The problem is the location
Anyway, how about on the mountain
far away
Good idea
There's no other people around
this area
Good, let's land
Blinking movement
Cool, we are in the mountain
Let's go play
There's shouldn't be anybody
complaint if we play here
How the neighbor won't say anything
for they're noisy
It's better the forest is bigger
It's getting late, need to
prepare supper
What should we have for dinner
tonight?
Radish and onion
Fish from yesterday
Then I make some stew tonight
Or should I make curry
Caught it
Mapo Dofu is good too
It's so hard to decide
Ah, where is this ?
Play for a longtime
It's so fun
Let's get back to where we were
We'll come next time
Where is you mom?
I'm so hungry
Where is this place?
I just come out shopping
Why it turned out to be
like this?
It can't be
Perhaps we left mom in the mountain
Must be Nobita and
Doraemon playing tricks
I had enough
(Dream walker)
What are you doing,
Doraemon?
Tell me to eat red bean cake ?
Ok, I am eating now
Who let you eat my Mashu
Give it back to me
It hurts
You wake me up from a
interesting dream
Can you be walking and
dreaming the same time
Right, this is called the
Dream walker
You can correct mistakes in
your dream
Good
I was think of having a
happy dream
Let me borrow it
Have to pick a dream first
What? We become poor
suddenly
YE$, WE BYE SO POOP
Daddy lost his job
Mom is sick
So heart breaking
Turn on the poor situation dream
Can't do anything about him
Nobita
Mom, you better lie down
Daddy asked you to may pocket
Daddy bumped into a truck
Daddy
Dad
What's wrong with you ?
Daddy, how can you just left me?
Daddy
What?
Don't say those unlucky words
So, I said
Better pick a good dream
What do you want?
Ah...
Ok, how about war dream
No, I'm too scared, forget it
How about romantic
No, I'm a boy
Should be more proud
Hurry and decide if you're a man
That's right, how about ventures
Dream of ventures ?
The magic mirror is the stage
Fighting with the monsters
Save the poor
And then find a lot of treasures
You ask a lot
That will do
Magic mirror look just like real
In the horrible place
Only me and my dog Doraemon
What? I'm a dog?
I'm a cat style mechanic with
background
Are you kidding
HEY
Escape without your master
what a coward
Even if it's only me
the venture continued
It hurts
It hurts, so hurt
No matter how hard it is
It won't scared me
I'll be brave
Monsters from out of no where
Come close to them maybe accidents
Be careful
not to be found
What?
Finally
enter the code of Magic place
It shows up
How horrible
Help
Be careful
really
Can't be careless any moment
What is this?
It's dangerous
Escaped straight ahead
Monsters are playing with butterfly
Invite me to joint ?
To catch butterfly with this
is kind of hard
So, the spirit is monster
Nobita still walking and
dreaming the same time
Makes me worried
This time it's flying octopus
They are crying
Were fighter! up by ropes
The monsters caught them
Ok, I'll rescue you at once
Monsters ahead
release the octopus at once
Or...
What?
Nobita is so proud
I'm the messenger of justice
Dorn, rascle
The main character is in danger
Really like a dream of venture
But it hurts so much
Just as I thought
Stop, stop it
Doraemon, my dear dog
You're here to save me
I'm SO angry
It's about time for you
to be awake
The dream has to continue
Have to find some more treasure
He, Doraemon
Before we find the huge treasure
I'll not be awake
Really
Finding treasures is duty of dog
I don't remember
I have that duty
It's around here
Great. Good job
Take the shoveler
Ok
If we can find 10 coins
that'd good enough
Doraemon,
don't be nonsense
Doraemon
Uncle
Great. You're just in time
Happy new year
Happy new year, give me the red...
It's terrible. Just when
You should have know
Red pocket money
I almost forgot
Here you are
Thank you
Nobita, look
That is it
Worth of about couple billion Yen
treasure
What? It's only a thousand Yen
Don't mix dream and
reality together
So embarrassing
( Ghost lamp)
I don't know
Mom is very busy
Don't say that
Tell me some horror stories
Please
Tonight, at Nobita's house we are
going to have ghost story meeting
I have to tell some ghost stories
Mom, I want to make everyone
trembling
Can't understand
why you are like this
Then, I'll tell you
a horror story
Long long time ago
A old grandma live the mountain
Does the old grandma looked
like this
It hurts
One day
Old grandma was preparing dinner
Suddenly, she felt uncomfortable
So, she went and laid down
After a day
Two days
Each day, she got more sick
Finally, on the 7th day
Did she die ?
She recovered
Just like that ?
Yes
That's not horror
No such thing
Because when she had the meal
of the 7th day
Old grandma was so scared
Mom really
what so horror about this
Doraemon, tell me
whatever as long as it's horror story
Ghost lamp
Take this out and tell
a horror story
Then accidents will happen
afterward
I don't know any horror story
You can make one up
Anyway, it guaranty horror
Really
It's quite in the mood
I'm so scared since the
very beginning
I'm not afraid at all
Tell the most horror story wins
Good, I'll make everyone scared
Me too
The plats were 10 a set
Servant broke any of it
Would be killed by the Sumorai
Since then, every night
There would be voice of counting
plats..1,2,3,4..
You can hear the sound of ghost
grandma's step
Then paper door would be open
silently
A big knife shown
Did you see a face like this?
It's a horror face
So scary
It seems that I have heard all
of this before
It's not horror at all
And he is scared to half death
Too tricky, just scared all
by yourself
Hurry Nobita It's your turn
Impossible
I mean whatever I say
Accident will happen afterward
What are you nonsense about?
Use those word to scare people
is old
Ok, all right. You just try to
scare everyone
Then, let's begin
I won't be responsible
for result
Quite an atmosphere
Long long time ago
How horror
If you keep like this,
the story can't go on
Be serious, please
Because breaking any import plate
Servants will be killed and
thrown into well
You copy me
The sound of broken plate
There's no one in the house
It's rat
Don't worry about that, go on
Don't
I have a bad feeling
No?
It's interesting
Please go on
Then...
Since then
Every night
The light of the lamp would suddenly
be put off
It's just the cold wind
Continue
A voice of hatry coming out
One, two
Three...Four...
Be quiet, silence
Because,because
That's not real,
you heard it wrong
I really did
Impossible for you to hear
Never mind that
Tell something different
Eight, nine
No matter how many counted, only
this much
Search the house up side down
can only find 910 Yen coins
And triped at the kitchen and broke
the plate
This is a poor house
Then, sound of steps echos back
at the hall way
Ta ta ta ta...
Finally, stopped at the door
The parper door were open
Once the door was opened
A knife shown
Scare me
It's police Help
Stop Don't run
So I say
Ghost lamp is horror
I know I lost
All right, you are the champagne
Great
It's too easy
If I knew it I'd tell some
horrible ghost face story
Didn't turn off the lamp
Doraemon will it be...Will it...
Ghost face
It's here It's here
So impolite
I'm just doing my skin care
(Predictable Diary How horror)
La, la, la
So interesting
So tiresome
Where did you all go ?
We're going up to the mountain
How about that ? Envy us?
Tomorrow, I'm going to the beach
for 3 days
Pity
It's going to rain for 3 days
How did you know
No matter what others said
This is set
long time ago
That's too bad
Bye
That guy
Went to the mountain or beach
Too rush on the time schedule
Summer vacation is only this much
Why did it turn out like this
I didn't think about anything
Right
I don't know it would be like this
Ya
Daddy, mommy
Tomorrow, we'll go to a movie
The Universe Super man is on
No
I don't want to go out anymore
Even if we don't go for now
When it's time, we'll still go
This is set
long time ago
It seems to be a bit too much
Doraemon won't let me borrow
good thing often
Should make a good use of it
Predictable Diary
It has the future affairs in it
Things will happen on time
Then, what would happen today ?
Ah, what did it say here?
Come back from the mountain,
then straight to bed
You're too lazy
Write again: Get up at once and study
No
No, Doraemon
I don't want to be like that
This is better
I'm going to erase it
Can't erase it at all
I don't want to study hard
Immediately stop studying
What a horror diary
Once you write on it, you have to
follow it
Then...
If write on something impossible
what would happen then?
For instance
It's not just rain
it's candy rain
No matter what is impossible
It's candy
So incredible
Kind of scary now
Just now the sky has candy rain
Those were the candy in the
cargo plane
The door were broken
So the candy floated out the plane
to the ground
It's all because of me
Lying
Impossible to have that diray
Whatever you write it happens
The problem is it really happens
See, this is predictable diary
Good, let me try
Don't write anything weird
Can't never do that
Let me see
Nobita was beatened up by Jian
Strangled by Shizuka
Eaten by lion
Oh, no
How can you write that
Dorn
It hurts so bad, Nobita
How dare of you to beat me
what did I do wrong?
No...
Ah, I'm sorry
Urgent news
Lion escaped from the zoo
Lion escaped
What? How can it be
See, Suneo, it all comes true
No of mind business
What should I do ?
I'm finished
Doraemon, what should I do ?
Lion is still at large
How can you make trouble like that?
Because Suneo...
No way to change this
No way at all ?
I'll be eaten by lion,
and you don't care
Doraemon, no such thing
Don't know
But this is the only way
The lion is caught
Luckily, no one is hurted
Safe
Almost got killed
So I said you're too much
It's better predictable diary not
exists
(Pitcher's Hat)
Strike
You're pretty good, Suneo
It's hard for people to
hit your ball
Yes, I have been practice
Cool
I'm going to throw now
Good, throw the ball
Strike, good throw, Suneo
Keep it UP
Let me try, ok?
You ?
Nobita, you ?
Ok, you try it
Suneo, are you ready ?
Throw a good one. Come
Throwing now
What in the world ?
Really
Nobita, where are you aiming at?
Sorry, I won't miss it this time
My hand was trembling just now
Be quiet and throw the ball
Be serious
I will
Miss it again
Dorn
You have no right to pitch
You're so terrible
I'll never accompany you to practice
any more
I don't want to play ball
I'll never play ball again
I can't control the ball
No such thing
the difference is the practice
As long as you practice
anybody can improve
Ok, let's start practicing
Use this to practice
Try it
No
No matter how hard I practice
it won't work
I'm not talented
Don't be so disappointed
Anyway, as long as I hit the target,
right?
Pitcher's hat
Wear this hat
You can become the best pitcher
Just like you want to hit the target
You don't have to look at it
You still can hit it
Impossible, heysu
Wow, how amazing
So, you must have a good performance
Come, let's practice
Show them, let Suneo see the different
side of you
It's ok If I can't play
baseball, that would be ok
Then why do you practice
For example
Lay down like this
Blow your nose
If you throw away paper like this
Mom will scold you, right?
And then?
And then so does
the book you finished
Back to the same place, right?
You are so hopeless
You're so young and already so
troublesome
You are not going to have
good future
Nobita, where is the change ?
You need to give them back to me
What is this?
Nobita, how can you fool around
like this
What if hit on the eyes
Someone will get hurt
Understand ? Do you hear me ?
Answer me, you answer me
All right
Mom is really nagging
Yes, yes
But
why is Nobita so slow ?
Really, that boy is too slow
Last time, he was terrible
pitching balls
Saying something bad about me
Good
That guy is so dumb
What is this
Suneo
Where is this chewing gum from ?
Take it off quick
Teach you all a lesson for tell
bad of me
Hellow
Nobita's resident
Hello, Shizuka
He's in, Just a second
Shizuka is on the phone, Nobita
It's Shizuka
But it's so troublesome
Wait
What if I mail myself?
Mail me to Shizuka's house
Flying
Great
Get here so soon
I can see it now
Pass Shizuka's house
Where am I flying to ?
Strange
He was here just now
Nobita, your telephone
Strange, where will he be?
Shizuka called from Baheidou
lt's very special
(Tea pot tape recorder)
ok?
Suneo, you still look the same
It's been half month since I left
for Brazil
Today, I'll send you Brazilian
music
My pen pal is Shuya who had moved
to Brazil
How I miss her
It's been along I hear her voice
It's very convenient
Can I borrow your tape recorder
Me too
We don't have tape recorder at home
It's no use even if we borrow it
What do we buy tape recorder for?
What for? Of course
I want to listen to the voice
Don't mention that again. Did you
do home work?
Finish it before you go out and play
Understand ?
It's nothing to do with this
Mom will tell me to do my home work
first
Just like a tape recorder
Tape recorder
I want one too
What is this ?
What is this?
It's my voice
What is this, Doraemon ?
That's the sound of tea pot
Machine records Nobita's voice
What an interesting tea pot
Go and show it the everyone
They'll be surprised
Finish your home work?
I'll do it tonight, it's the same
Right
Finish the home work before play
Study hard
I love to study
Writing the home work is fun
Hurry and write
Doraemon
remember to break one from time to time
I'm going out
Quietly
Nobita is doing it again...
Finish the home work before play
Study hard
I love to study
Doing home work is fun
So smart
Make some desert for him
Finish the home work one by one
Nobita keeps the record,
would share with others
He snatched away my tape recorder
Jian always bully others
Ok
Then, I'll record bad things about
Jian
Each times sounds alike, I'm touched
Go
Nobita is a fat boy
What? Who ?
Dorn...
Ah?
What is this buble thing ?
Jian is a greedy
Jian is an idiot
Jian you bad
Ah?
Jian is a big ape
Jian is a bad boy
Jian is bad, Jian is a rascle
Jian's music idiot
Who says bad things about me
behind me
Come out now, at once
Where are you hiding? Come out now
It hurts
Why are you throwing things in the
house?
Mom, but...
Nobita really shouldn't
I just do as he told me
Sorry
I'll never forgive him again
That feels better
I'm back
Doraemon
Nobita, mom is angry now
What should I do, Doraemon ?
Go apology to your mom, she's so
angry
With you standing at the door
I can't get in
No more, go and apology, hurry
No
Nobita, come in here
I am sorry
Please, forgive me
Forgive me
I'll never do it again
Please
I'm sorry
I'm truly sorry
Since he apologized,
please forgive him
Mom is so pretty
Please
Mom is so soft
So, I'm sorry
You see
Please forgive me
Look
The end